Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ nguyenquang291 (LinkedIn) zalo.me/0333953916 (Other)

Top Skills

Laravel

Yii

Core Java

Nguyen Quang

Software Engineer

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Summary

Thanks for visiting my profile:

Web development

Experience with Yii2, Laravel in PHP

Experience with Spring Boot, Spring Cloud (Alibaba, Gateway) in JAVA

Database

Experience with SQL databases : MySQL, Oracle ...

Experience with NoSQL databases : Redis, Elasticsearch

Cloud Service

Experience with AWS (S3)

Other tools:

Experience with Kafka

Experience with Docker/Kubernetes

Experience with Git, Gitlab, and Github

Experience with ELK Stack

I can guarantee that you'll be satisfied with my work output as I am a very hard-working and diligent person.

I'm looking forward to all the work opportunities!

Experience

Spower Media
Software Engineer
September 2024 - Present (7 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Viettel Post

Software Engineer

February 2023 - December 2023 (11 months)

Page 1 of 2

Enuy Corporation Joint Stock Company Middle Software Engineer July 2023 - October 2023 (4 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Aladintech.co Project Manager March 2022 - February 2023 (1 year) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

ĐH Bách Khoa Hà Nội · (2017 - 2020)